Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his trials, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Continuing their assault upon humanity, the ten elves known as the Apostles of Sephira brought forth the Shadow Palace,
the border between this world and the next that lay inside Clover Castle.
When we place the final magic stone into its pedestal inside the palace, the elves' great reincarnation will be complete.
Of course, a price must be paid for our use of these bodies. Sadly, their human souls will be sent to the underworld.
Kay, so there's a magical space growing over there.
Kay, Kay, sounds like our cue to head that way.
You won't stop the Apostles of Sephira!
It's one thing after another. Can't these jerks just give us a break?
Fortunately, reinforcements arrived.
Kay, is that...
Here we are!
You guys okay?!
A huge bull!
No way!
You bunch of dumbasses!
Better work on that entrance!
Curse you humans!
Bring in whatever reinforcements you like. You're still no match for the elves.
Thanks to Asta and the others, it appeared as though the tables had turned. However...
Don't tell me this key is what I think it is.
I know her!
It's the captain of the Coral Peacocks!
Did she get possessed too?!
Dream magic. Glamour world.
Dorothy Unsworth, captain of the Coral Peacocks, had also reincarnated as an elf.
She used her magic to teleport Vanessa and the others into the dream world.
Welcome to the dream world.
Let's!
There's nothing in my mindieren
They celebrate a challenge
and it doesn't matter to me
do this has no one
So let's understand
zero
save my life
that get out of dance
everything тебя納んな
except for there,
all the knowledge
light
ll it
love
through me
I can't see very well without my glasses, but it sure seems fun!
This place is freaky. Anyone know where the heck we are?
The captain of the coral peacock's magic. I don't know what else it could be.
Rouge wasn't able to evade it, because she couldn't identify it as an attack spell.
This is the best! It's one of the most powerful spells a mage can produce!
Man, I'm freaking out!
Will you please just rein it in?
Wow, this place goes on forever. There's no end to it.
Huh? Don't be a moron! How's that even possible?
It's a lot more likely than the possibility of you becoming smart!
What the hell did you say to me?!
You're in the glamour world now, in this place. The impossible becomes real.
Welcome... to the world where I control everything.
The bitches!
Everything here is how I wish it to be.
I don't know what that thing is, but it's really big!
And it just keeps getting bigger!
I wonder if it's tasty!
I hate to disappoint...
...but you have no chance...
...of winning.
...and I'll sleep.
Good night forever.
How dare I try to eat us instead?!
No, we died!
Get a load of this, you stupid pig!
The result was altered...
...so...
...that magic really does influence fate.
That little red cat is so stinking cute!
You're not one of the black bulls, you know.
If you stray too far, her magic won't affect you.
Be careful.
I get it!
Just you guys!
There'd have to be limits on a spell this great...
...dream magic...
...and bread magic!
These two witches are super cool!
Wanna research...
...mah!
I feel like she's bad news.
Think so?
Here, eat!
When you use magic, you have to eat up so you can recover your mana!
That magic is great!
You wouldn't happen to be a witch, would you?
No, ma'am.
I just really like to cook and eat!
An inexhaustible magic supply and absolute evasion.
This won't be easy.
If this ridiculous place is also a world of magic...
...then all we have to do to get out is defeat her!
Looks like it!
No.
Can she use any magical attribute in this place?
Oh wow, I wonder what her limits are!
Wow, this is fun!
Weirdo, this isn't fun at all!
I mean, what are we even supposed to do?
She's invincible.
Your magic's not that interesting!
Hate to tell ya!
The hell did you just say?!
Well then, do you wanna fight me?
This is not the time to be playing around.
Yeah, she's right!
I'm the cornerstone of our defense.
And Charmy's vital to mana recovery.
We can't both stay stuck here.
We have to hurry back to the others.
But how?
All I can do is help us evade with Rouge's magic.
Time to recover your mana!
Come on, eat Vanessa!
Hurry!
No!
Come on, Vanessa!
Eat!
I'm gonna slap all of you if I get fat from this!
There has to be some kind of limit to her healing abilities.
An ever-flowing pool of water.
Which has bladefish continually spawning from it.
A never-ending onslaught.
Stop!
Stop off my nose!
Crap!
That's not good!
Oh, water!
Hmm.
Say there, lightning boy!
Think you could attack that overgrown puddle?
Yeah?
I'm not sure if I can destroy something that big, though.
That's fine!
Just give it your all!
Now, lightning magic!
Thunderbolt Destruction!
Well, that sure didn't work.
Okay then, fire protozoan.
It's your turn.
Who are you calling a fire protozoan, jerk?
Oh, come on.
Put your eagle aside and shoot it with everything you've got.
Who the hell do you think I am?
Oh!
If I guess correctly, and that pool really is made of water...
Huh?
It's gonna explode!
Yay!
Intensity!
That's what I'm talking about!
Whoa!
What just happened?
Ah!
I broke the water down electrically, and then set fire to what was left.
Huh?
Well, if you unleash lightning magic and flame magic on water, you can create an explosion
big enough to destroy an entire mountain!
What the?
How could you make us do something so reckless?
Who cares?
You could evade with the cat.
Oh!
I'll try that with Noelle's magic next.
Anyway, the experiment made a few other things clear to me, too.
First of all, what she's generating are actual objects that she's visualized.
Which means real world principles work on them, too!
Yummy!
And a real life, dirty fish!
Secondly, because of that, she's unable to manipulate the spells we cast, nor can she
control the resulting phenomena!
That makes sense.
Otherwise, that explosion in Rouge's ability to manipulate fate wouldn't have worked.
And then, thirdly, it's still going to be really difficult to beat her.
Geez, you'd think she'd ease up a little.
We'd better hurry up and find a way out of this place.
Sorry.
You don't have that kind of time.
Charmy!
I'm so sleepy.
Hey!
What are you talking about?
This is no time!
Uh-oh!
Oh no.
This is...
How unfortunate.
You can't evade the drowsiness.
That's how it is.
Everything that exists in Glamour World will eventually get drowsy.
Worse yet, those who fall asleep will never awaken again.
Who are you talking to?
How?
I managed to stay awake during all of Yali's all-nighters!
This is nothing!
This isn't good.
I don't know what we can do to evade this attack.
You will sink into the sleep of death.
For in this enchanted space, you cannot resist.
Aw, everything was already blurry.
Now it's getting even blurrier.
Not having my glasses really sucks.
Oh yeah!
Hey!
Check it out!
Do you have any idea what these are?
If not, I'll tell ya!
Glasses!
Like em?
What are you babbling on about glasses for?
Now's not the time to worry about...
Yay!
Look!
What?!
She just made those.
Where did those come from?
Everything in this world does as she sees fit.
That's why the objects that she visualized in her head materialized.
Now if you ask me, what this world needs most is an exit, exit, exit!
Make one, please!
It's hard not to think of something once your mind has already visualized it.
Hooray for the power of suggestion!
Aw, hell yeah!
She's only invincible in this dumb glamour world!
If we can escape it, we'll figure this out.
What the heck's going on?
It's all the same no matter how far we go.
We can't even find any walls, let alone licked.
Then there's the faint key that I'm feeling.
Damn it.
You think that-
Care, care!
Looks to me like someone's magic is causing us to lose our way.
Huh.
So I guess you noticed it too, beanpole weirdo.
Right back at you, you meathead.
They've got some nerve hiding from us.
I'm impatient.
I want to dice them up already.
Let me have them.
No, they're mine to slash us.
I found them first, it's only fair that I do it.
What are you talking about?
I found them first.
I did.
It was me!
Ugh, you were such a pain in the ass!
Take care!
The only bird slashes the worm!
They're right there!
What are you slashing, you jerk?
The enemy's totally right there!
No way!
Don't be dumb, they're right over there!
I mean, did you not even know how to hit an enemy?
Well, you didn't hit anything either!
Ah!
Ah, whatever!
I am officially done with you, useless scrawny freak!
That's my life, stupid beefcake!
Get over there!
No, you go!
No, you!
Yikes, that was too close for comfort.
Though I suppose in my warp space, they were both correct, technically speaking.
Thank goodness I rolled a six.
That should keep them busy for a little while.
With dice magic, the higher the number, the more effective it will be in the situation at hand.
I won't let anyone get in the way of the Apostles of Sephiroth.
I would appreciate it if these two could keep quiet just a bit longer.
There's no way I can keep this off anymore!
Their overall power is much higher than ours.
I'm about to reach my limit!
This is pointless, just give up already!
I don't think so!
We're not done yet!
What should I do?
Think!
If only I could get into my dark form.
But, I don't think he's gonna give me a chance for that.
Pasta!
The others!
I hate that all we can do is watch!
Big Brother.
I know.
We must keep Licht and everyone waiting a bit longer.
Eklat, you know what to do.
Here we go.
Huh?
Asta!
This spell!
It's the same one Ghosh used to avoid attacks!
Yes, come right this way, kid.
Licks demon destroyer sword.
It severs all cause and effect relationships nearby.
He can nullify Eklat's eye magic, so I'll get rid of him first.
Yeah.
No thank you!
You can't!
What do you think?
I'm not going to do that.
I'm not going to do it.
But...
I'm not going to do that.
Asta!
This spell...
It's the same one Ghosh used to avoid attacks!
Yes, come right this way, kid.
Licks demon destroyer sword.
It severs all cause and effect relationships nearby.
He can nullify Eklat's eye magic, so I'll get rid of him first.
Thank you!
Can you evade attacks with your eyes closed?
I can't!
With Ki!
In that case, how about this?
So many!
Not good!
Pasta, no!
This time, it's our turn.
We're going to save him!
Go!
I'm going to rip right through that pitiful attempt.
What?
Here we go!
Now I can fight!
You're mine!
You just...
Looked!
The magic item in his left eye!
Crap!
I've had enough of you, brat!
I will destroy every piece of you, so you can't fight us again!
I'll never undo the binding spell in time!
There's no way!
Asta's in trouble!
Oh no!
And my magic can't reach nearly that high up!
Asta!
Goodbye now!
We're here, Asta!
We're here!
Asta!
Poison magic!
Violet Shihiraman!
Asta!
I owe you one, guys!
Thanks!
That actually wasn't too bad.
Asta!
Just as we thought!
Gosh is way stronger than usual like this!
Still...
Asta!
Apache!
Many mages use magic to reinforce their natural defenses, and Henry is no exception.
But, in Henry's case, his very life depends on it.
His blood vessels, muscles, and organs are incredibly frail.
He will die unless he continually reinforces them with magic.
However, he'd been granted a constitution that absorbed magical power.
One which enabled him to gain it from others.
Despite being born into a renowned noble line, his body was deemed too frail.
His family and the rest of the world could not accept him for what he was.
This can't be! If we continue to harbor that thing, it will only bring disgrace to the great name of Legoland.
How can you speak of our child that way?
We have no other choice! This is for our family.
Placing too much value on status can warp one's morals.
Henry's parents gave him very little.
A house in the forest that stored up magic, but remained unseen by others.
A sad and lonely existence.
This is just as it should be.
All I ever do is cause trouble for people.
You must be that mysterious ghost I've been hearing about.
Actually, sir, I'm not a ghost at all.
Cool, well, my name is Yami.
I'm a brand new magic knight captain, and I'm looking for a hideout.
This place seems to be a good fit.
Before he came to me that day, I was basically dead.
You should live. It's more convenient.
But I...
I mean, think about it.
If there's a bunch of rowdy magic knights causing a ruckus all the time, it might even make you feel better.
That's how my house became the hideout for the Black Bulls.
And up until that moment, I was.
I'm alive today.
And it's all because of them.
That's why I feel this way.
I don't care what happens to me.
I'll save my friend.
I swear.
追い続けてた夢が
一人歩きになってた
次の道への地図は
どこかに忘れてきた
行方すら決めず彷徨った
夜道が少しぼやけた
人生は全長だ
そう感じることもある
自分らしく
とは何も反対とはない
愛なんて知らない
笑うのも痛い
でも本当は強くないよ
歩くべき道を
ずっと手探りだけで
探してる
遠い人歩きの回想は
情緒に行ってた
神の中に
ほっ toll
見捨てる
次のags
you saw
I'm gonna stop you two no matter what
I will turn you back into the normal Goshen Marie
No, my name is Draw
My name is Eklat
And we are never going to turn back now
But I would like to learn more about this human named Goshen
This doll that looks just like Eklat
I had it when I reincarnated
It's just too cute
And these, the pictures of her in different outfits
He is truly a man of culture
This guy knows what's cute
Big brother?
Oh, sorry, nothing weird going on over here, no?
You're from Marie Toll and her pictures!
Did you see?
I did
Why can't I move?
Black Clover
Page 112
Humans who can be trusted
I'll save my friends
No matter what it takes
Tell me about how much
You can throw more
Pode not be
Yeah, we're Sociedad
Most probably
we thought
Really
Oh,
you
Know
Well
Yes
And
You
So
I jeśli
What